You are here:

1. [Home](https://help.law/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Information we gather
---------------------

In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.

Our registration form requests that you provide certain contact and profile information. That information includes but may not be limited to: name, address, email address and phone number. All personal information collected by Help.law is stored safely on a secure server.

Please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to, processed and stored in overseas locations. The data protection laws may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the respective countries. By using our services or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in overseas locations.

Collection of Personal Details
------------------------------

Details that may be collected and held for processing include:

* Information that identifies you, such as your name, address, date of birth and gender;
* Your email address;
* Your telephone number
* Case Information

How we use the information we gather
------------------------------------

The personal information we collect includes your name, email address, phone number, and physical address. We also collect other information about your illness or injury, all of which is clearly labeled at the time of collection. Our primary use of your personal information is to conduct a preliminary analysis of your information to determine whether you meet our criteria for follow-up contact. We may contact you to verify your information. We may also transfer your personal information to a law firm, which may contact you to verify your information and further evaluate your claims. We may also transfer your contact information in a hashed manner to marketing partners for the purpose of serving personalized ads or building audiences that have characteristics of users like you. We automatically collect certain information from visitors to our site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. We do not respond to your browser’s “do not track” signals or other mechanisms for indicating your preference regarding the collection personally identifiable information.

Visitor Options
---------------

If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe by contacting [webmaster@help.law](mailto:webmaster@help.law) or using the unsubscribe link on any email correspondence you receive from us.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website.

Our use of cookies
------------------

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. Also they may be used to track your return visits to the website.

3rd party advertising companies may also use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Telephone Consumer Protection Act
---------------------------------

By submitting your Information to us on a Site, you agree that this is an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, as amended (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. This allows us to contact you via telemarketing even if your telephone number is listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists.

Where you provide “prior express written consent” within the meaning of the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (“TCPA”), you consent to receive telephone calls, including artificial voice calls, pre-recorded messages and/or calls delivered via automated technology and text and SMS messages to the telephone number(s) that you provided from us and the marketing partners. You are not required to provide this consent to obtain access to the Offers, products or services, and your consent simply allows us to contact you via these means. If you: (a) have your telephone number reassigned to another person; (b) give up your telephone number; (c) port your telephone number to a landline or vice versa; or (d) otherwise stop using that telephone number; you are required to inform us

Merely accessing one of our Sites without providing your express written consent for TCPA purposes does not constitute your consent to receive telemarketing calls or text/SMS messages

To ensure that consumers' inquiries are handled accurately, courteously, and promptly, phone calls between you and Help.Law or any of our partners, affiliates, agents, case managers, paralegals, and/or attorneys may be recorded. We may from time to time make calls and/or send text messages to you at any telephone number associated with your account. The manner in which these calls or text (SMS) messages are made to you may include, but is not limited to, the use of prerecorded/artificial voice messages and/or an automatic telephone dialing system. You certify, warrant, and represent that the telephone numbers you have provided to us are your contact numbers. You represent that you are permitted to receive calls at each of the telephone numbers you have provided to us. You agree that Morgan & Morgan may send emails to you at any email address you provide us, or use other electronic means of communication to the extent permitted by law.
